コードギアス反逆のルルーシュR2 TURN 18　第二次　東京　決戦
TURN 18　第二次　東京　決戦
Taking up the request of U.F.N. resolution
number one for the liberation of Japan,
超合集国決議第壱號　日本解放の要請を受け
the Black Knights engaged
in a landing operation...
黒の騎士団は 神聖ブリタニア帝国の植民地
into the Holy Britannian Empire
colony known as Area 11.
エリア11に対し上陸作戦を展開する
Against Bismarck Waldstein, the Knight
of One encamped on the Kyushu coast,
キュウシュウ沿岸に陣取る　ナイトオブワン
ビスマルク ヴァルトシュタインに対し
clashed the main force, under the
command of Field Marshall Li Xing-ke.
総司令　リー シンクー率いる主力部隊が激突
Using that as a distraction,
a detachment of Black Knight forces...
それを陽動として 黒の騎士団の別動部隊が
began advancing on
the Tokyo settlement.
トウキョウ租界にむけて進撃を開始した
However, at that point, neither Zero
nor anyone in the Black Knights...
しかし 待ち受けるシュナイゼル軍に
大量破壊兵器フレイヤがあることは
knew of the existence of F.L.E.I.J.A.,
この時点では ゼロをはじめ
a weapon of mass destruction in the
possession of Schneizel's forces there.
黒の騎士団側は 誰ひとりとして知る由もなかった
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
Kireigoto dake jaa ikirenai
Pretty words alone won't sustain you
Yasashisa dake jaa iyasenai
Kindness alone won't heal you
Ubawareta nowa nanda
What is it that was stolen from you
Kawaranai sekai de
In this unchanging world
Kikoetekita nowa nanda
What is it that you hear
Shikisai no uta
A song of color
Everything is bright...
Kudakechitta yume wo
Let our crumbled dreams resound
Asu no hate ni hibikaseru you ni
At the edge of tomorrow
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Bokura hitotsu ni
Becomes one with us
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
FINAL BATTLE TOKYO II
黒の騎士団 斑鳩艦隊に告げる
Message to Black Knight Ikaruga fleet!
ゲフィオン ディスターバーによって
The Gefjun Disturbers
have immobilized all utilities,
トウキョウ租界のライフライン 通信網
communications, and pre-fifth generation
Knightmares in the Tokyo settlement!
そして 第五世代以前のナイトメアは機能を停止した
敵の戦力は半減している
The enemy's military
might has been halved!
各主要施設を叩き トウキョウ租界の戦闘継続能力を奪い取れ
Hit all major facilities and take away the
settlement's ability to keep fighting us!
シュナイゼル率いる　主力戦闘部隊が到着するまでが勝負となる
We have to accomplish this...
before the main forces under
Schneizel's command arrive.
防衛戦を敷きつつ ブリタニア政庁を孤立させろ
Once we establish a defense line,
we'll cut off the government bureau!
If we can arrest Viceroy Nunnally,
then victory will be ours!
ナナリー総督をおさえれば 我が軍の勝利だ
ナナリー総督 ゼロが ゼロがあらわれました
Viceroy Nunnally, it's Zero!
Zero has appeared!
ゼロ
Zero!
ゼロがきてくれた？！
Zero's come?!
いい顔だ
That's a better face for you.
君はそっちが本当みたいだな
That looks more like the real you.
でもすまない
But I'm sorry. Your wish won't come true.
君の望みはかなわない
この私と トリスタンがいる限りは
Not as long as I and my Tristan
are here to defend it.
まずは環状線沿いに展開するゲフィオン ディスターバーを排除するとして
First of all, we need to dispose of...
the Gefjun Disturbers set up
along the rail loop line.
だせるかな ランスロットは
We can dispatch the Lancelot, can't we?
That should be asked of
Sir Kururugi's pride, shouldn't it?
それは 枢木卿のプライドにおききするべきかと
ふふっ戦場でそんな表現をきくことになるとはね
I never thought I'd ever hear such
words spoken on a battlefield.
ニーナさん！あなたには無理です
Nina, there's no way you can do this!
でも このままじゃトウキョウ租界もゼロに！
But if we don't do something,
Zero will capture the Tokyo settlement!
だからさあ 君はデヴァイサーじゃなくて科学者なの！
Even so, you're a scientist, not a Devicer!
FCCを使えば 政庁にいくくらいは！
If I use the F.C.C., I can at least
get to the government bureau!
君にフレイヤを撃つ覚悟はあるのかい？
But are you prepared to
actually fire the F.L.E.I.J.A.?
It takes more than that, though.
You have to be prepared to NOT fire it.
それだけじゃない撃たない覚悟も必要なんだ
藤堂朝比奈と千葉に政庁の制空権をおさえさせろ
Tohdoh! You, Asahina, and Chiba will establish
air supremacy over the government bureau!
承知
Wilco!
さて 問題は敵軍第六世代以降のナイトメアだが
Now then, the problem remaining is the enemy
6th-generation and above Knightmares. Rolo!
ロロ そちらの突入状況はどうなっている？
How is your infiltration proceeding?
咲世子のチームが先行しているよ
Sayoko's team is going on ahead.
僕たちもこれから合流するから
We'll be rendezvousing with her shortly.
よし必ずナナリーを確保しろ
Good. Be sure you take Nunnally alive.
ん？やはりきたか スザク
So, Suzaku... You've come.
ルルーシュは ゼロは僕が償わせるしかない
I'm the only one who can make Lelouch...
Make Zero atone for what he's done.
きこえるか ゼロ 戦闘を停止しろ
Do you hear me, Zero?
Cease this battle at once!
This unit is equipped with
a high-yield tactical warhead.
こちらは重戦術級の弾頭を搭載している
使用されれば 4000万リータ以上の被害をもたらす
If I use it, it will inflict over forty million
liters of damage! Before I do that!
その前に
おまえのいうことなど信じられるか
As if I'd believe anything
you have to say! Jeremiah!
ジェレミア！
えっ
イエス　ユアマジェスティ
Yes, Your Majesty!
ジェレミア卿ですか？なぜ！
Lord Jeremiah, is that you?! Why?!
枢木スザク君には借りがある
Suzaku Kururugi, I owe you a debt.
You stir my feelings, make me feel less of a man.
However, in this place...
情もあるひけめもある
しかしこの場は 忠義が勝る！
my loyalty wins out!
The Siegfried's?!
ジークフリートの
受けよ！忠義の嵐！
Now, take this!
The storm of my devotion!
くっあなたにどんな事情があろうと 今は！
Whatever circumstances drove
you to this, now isn't the time!
ふん
使えそうですねサザーランドジークは
The Sutherland Sieg seems to be effective.
Although...
でもねえ
えっ
ジークフリートのシステムをつかったワンオフの機体
We'll never be able to mass-produce a one-off
unit that uses the Siegfried's systems.
量産にはむかないのよねえ
それよりもおしえてほしいのは
What I'd like to know more is why
Jeremiah is on our side now.
なんでジェレミアが仲間になってんのかってことよ
加えて帝国の先槍と呼ばれた男まで
Besides, the man they called the
Spearhead of the Empire...
どうなっている？
What's going on? Why...
Why am I fighting Britannian forces?
なぜ なぜ 私は ブリタニア軍を敵にして
ギルフォードジェレミアに加勢し　枢木スザクを討て
Guilford!
Assist Jeremiah and shoot Suzaku Kururugi!
しかし 姫様枢木は
But Princess, Kururugi is!
説明している時間はない非常時だ
There's no time to explain!
It's an emergency!
私を信じて戦ってくれないか
Can't you trust me and just fight?
ジェレミア卿！私はこんな闘いをおわらせたくて
Lord Jeremiah,
I just want to end this battle!
ならば 君にできるというのか？
You're saying you can do it?
Wipe away our lord's torment?
我が君の苦悩を消し去ることが！
みんなを巻き込む必要なんて
We don't have to involve
other people with this!
ギルフォード卿まで！
Lord Guilford! You, too?!
枢木互いに主君を持つ身悪く思うな！
Kururugi! We each serve our lords!
It's nothing personal!
スザク！フレイヤを撃って!今ならゼロを！
Suzaku! Fire F.L.E.I.J.A.!
Use this chance to kill Zero!
ごめん ニーナこれはつかわない
I'm sorry, Nina.
I won't use this. However!
でも ゼロは！
I swear... I will stop Zero!
僕が！
Excellent! Once we destroy Suzaku,
as I planned,
よし 作戦どおりここでスザクを始末すれば
ナナリーを取り返す障害は あっ
nothing will keep me
from taking back Nunnally!
ナイトオブラウンズの戦場に 敗北はない！
There is nothing which can defeat a
Knight of the Round on the battlefield!
ジノ すまない
Gino! Thank you!
こういうときは素直に喜べよ
You should sound happier about it.
ジェレミア卿？
Lord Jeremiah?
So, those suspicions about
Orange were true, huh?
オレンジの疑惑は本当だったようだな
オレンジ？
Orange? Heh...
ふっそれは我が忠誠の名前
That is the name of my loyalty!
この戦力シュナイゼルめ
All this military strength...
Damn you, Schneizel!
トウキョウ決戦をよんでいたのか
Did he anticipate my showdown in Tokyo?!
そうだ俺がそちらに合流するのはもう少し先になる
Right. I'll be rendezvousing with
you a little later than expecting.
うん わかった
Okay, understood. We've just
cleared up to the 13th floor now.
こっちは13階層間でクリアしたから
安心してナナリーは必ず僕がみつけだすよ
Don't worry.
I promise, I'll find Nunnally.
ああ頼んだぞ ロロ
Right. I'm counting on you, Rolo.
ナナリーさえとりかえせば
If you can just take back Nunnally,
I'll have no further need for you, Rolo.
ロロ お前は用済みなんだ
まかせて 兄さん
Don't worry, big brother.
I promise, I'll find Nunnally...
ナナリーは必ず僕がみつけだして
殺してやるから
Because I'm going to kill her.
兄さんの家族は　ぼくだけでいい
I'm the only family you need to have.
ロロ様
Master Rolo!
格納庫に向かった第２班から緊急連絡です
Emergency report from group
two headed towards the hangars.
優先事項第三位がみつかったと
They say they've sighted
priority item three.
いやです 私だけ逃げるなんて
I refuse!
I can't run away by myself!
これは宰相閣下のご指示です
The prime minister has ordered it!
Brother Schneizel did?
シュナイゼル兄様の？
他のものも 総督をおいて逃げるわけにはいきませんし
No one else can abandon this
place if the viceroy is left behind!
ふんこのガレスの前には
You're no match for my Gareth!
ひるむな！制空権を奪い取るんだ！と千葉
Keep at it!
We're grabbing air superiority here!
政庁はわたさん！
We won't give up
the government bureau!
しまった！藤堂さん
Oh, no... Tohdoh...
助かったよ 朝比奈
I owe you one, Asahina!
やりのこしてることがあるんでしょ
You've still got stuff to do, right?
A-Anyway, what do we do?
ゼロの指示では ナナリー総督をつかまえるまで
Zero's ordered us not to attack the bureau
itself until Viceroy Nunnally has been taken.
政庁そのものには攻撃するなということだけど
Zero, huh?
ゼロね
They're all...
They're all fighting, while I'm!
みんな！
みんな たたかってるのに
守り抜く！なんとしてでも
We will defend it! No matter what!
せめて我らグラストンナイツが功績をあげねば
If we Glaston Knights
can achieve a great feat,
ギルフォード卿が乱心された今
even though Lord Guilford
has lost his mind,
コーネリア皇女殿下のお立場は！
we can still save
Princess Cornelia's position!
答えてくれゼロ！
Answer me, Zero! If you started
this battle because of me, then...
自分が原因でこの戦いをはじめたのだとしたら！
うぬぼれるな
Don't be so conceited! You're a man who
betrayed his father and all of Japan!
おまえは親を 日本を裏切ってきた男だ
だから友情すら裏切る
It's only natural you would
betray your friendship as well!
ただそれだけだ
ん？ええい！
Why, you!
アーニャ？
Anya? Wait!
待ってくれ！
スザク ゼロはアーニャにまかせよう
Suzaku! Leave Zero to Anya!
あなたのシールドが上か
Which is stronger? Your shield
or my Stark Hadron cannon?
私のシュタルクハドロンが上か
こ これは
Wh-What the hell?!
いくら絶対守護領域でも
Even my Absolute Defense Field
can't withstand this for long!
蜃気楼 通信不能
Contact lost with the Shinkirō!
ゼロが？
How is Zero?
ナイトオブシックスと　交戦状態に入ったようです
He seems to be engaging the Knight of Six!
ハシモト隊への支持はどうしますか？と
What are your orders for Hashimoto unit?
クジュウクリの備えもありますが
We also have to defend Kujukuri.
あ ああ ええと
Um... That is...
ハシモトの連絡は俺に回せ！
Patch Hashimoto through to me!
杉山ゼロの援軍として動ける部隊は？と南
Sugiyama, do we have anyone
we can send to help Zero?!
それが 玉城しか
Well... Just Tamaki.
はい ナナリー総督は今脱出艇に
Right. Viceroy Nunnally
is in the escape craft.
ただ ゲフィオン ディスターバーが復旧されない限りは
But until the Gefjun Disturbers
are deactivated...
はい ナイトメアでは敵の標的になる可能性も
Right. We'd be a target for the enemy
if we escaped in a Knightmare.
はい よしなに
Right. Understood.
紅月カレンの抹殺は？
Who's going to execute Kallen Kouzuki?
Sir Georg.
ゲオルグ卿が
しかし よろしいのですか？ナナリー総督は
But, are you sure about this.
Viceroy Nunnally didn't...
It's for the viceroy's own good.
総督のためです
中途半端な自己主張など
Despite her halfhearted attempts
to assert herself...
咲世子さん
Sayoko!
ご無事で何よりです
You're looking well.
Master Rolo is going to get Miss Nunnally.
ナナリー様はロロ様が迎えにいかれました
私たちはカレン様にプレゼントをお届けに
We came to give you a present, Miss Kallen.
あと ミレイ様の元いいなづけが首謀者だと思うのですが
I think Miss Milly's former
fiancé was behind the changes,
一応取説らしきものもあったので
but there seems to be
a draft user's manual with it.
いかがいたしましょう？
Shall we try to get it working?
なんか ちがう
It's different, somehow...
戦線をのばしきるわけにもいかんし
We can't stretch our lines any further!
We're at the breaking point now!
このあたりが限界か！
イケブクロ スガモのディスターバー 完全解除しました
All Gefjun Disturbers in Ikebukuro
and Sugamo have been destroyed.
これで 第五世代以前のナイトメアも戦線に復帰できる
Now we can reinforce our lines with
5th-generation Knightmares and older.
政庁の防衛システムも回復しますし
We're also bringing the government
bureau's defense system back on line.
戦力的には逆転したね
The momentum of battle
has shifted in our favor.
あかりが！
The lights!
時間切れ？
We're out of time! Kinoshita!
Haven't you found the viceroy yet?!
木下！総督はまだみつからないの？と朝比奈
突入班からは 紅月隊長の件しかうっ
The assault teams have only reported
that they've freed Captain Kouzuki...
木下！
Kinoshita!
Hey! Are you okay?!
おい！大丈夫か？
作戦に 戻ってください自分は もう
Please... Get back... to the mission...
I'm not... gonna make it...
なんだよ！どこにもいねえじゃねえか！
What the hell?!
I can't find him anywhere!
ゼロはどこで戦ってるんだ！
Where's Zero fighting?!
He's my best pal!
俺の親友はよぉ！
もう少しで
A little more, and...
うっくっ また何かが
Again! Something is!
モルドレッド
What happened to the Mordred?
ゼロ
Zero! It seems the Black Rebellion
is destined to fail.
ブラックリベリオンは失敗に終わる定めだったようだなあ
またナイトオブラウンズか
Another Knight of the Round!
教えよう
Let me tell you...
大事なものとはなんだ？
What is the most precious
thing of all? That would be...
それは 命だ
your life!
So, the basic system is the same?
基本システムは同じか
We're still trying to determine
Master Zero's current location.
ゼロ様の位置は探索中です
敵味方識別情報を転送しますか
Shall I transfer the I.F.F. data?
ええ たのみます
Yes, please.
えっと
Let's see... How about
Guren S.E.I.T.E.N. Eight...
紅蓮聖天 八 でいいかしら
起動確認を
Confirm activation.
起動　確認しました
Activation, confirmed.
紅蓮出撃後 私たちは本来の作戦のもどりますが
Once the Guren is launched,
we'll return to our own mission.
Right. You take care of the viceroy.
I'll help Zero.
はい総督の件はたのみます私はゼロを
ええ それでは
Right. Well, then...
紅蓮
Guren!
聖天八極式　発進！
S.E.I.T.E.N. Eight Elements... LAUNCH!
Launch!
発進！
What the?! What's?!
なんだ？何が？
くわっ！もうしわけありません 父上
Father... Forgive me!
デヴィッド
David!
紅月だったのか？しかしあの機体は？
Was that Kouzuki?
But, that machine she's in!
このままでは
At this rate!
硬いだけがとりえのナイトメアフレームなど
That powerful armor is the only
good thing about your Knightmare!
Valkyrie squadron!
Don't let him go, no matter what!
ヴァルキリエ隊 絶対に離すなよ
Yes, my lord!
イエス　マイロード！
いけない！モルドレッドの時に消費したエナジーが！
I'm in trouble! I used up too
much energy with the Mordred!
ゼロ！きこえますか？ゼロ！
Zero! Do you read me, Zero?!
こちらの援軍はどうなった？！
Where are my reinforcements?!
まもなく玉城さんが
Tamaki will be there soon! But we've sighted
an enemy silhouette over the Pacific!
それより 太平洋上に敵影です
それがどうした！
What about it?!
ゼロ 俺だ
Zero, it's me!
敵影の正体は ブリタニア皇帝の旗艦らしいんだが
The enemy silhouette seems to be
the Britannian emperor's flagship!
何？！あいつもこのエリア11に？
What?!
He's coming to Area 11 as well?!
No. His Majesty is not
coming to the battlefield.
いや 陛下は戦場にはこられないよ
どうして言い切れるんですか?
Why are you so sure?
現実を 今日という日を大事にしていると思うかい？彼が
Do you think he cares about mundane things?
About the day which we call today?
Not him...
ゼロをはなしやがれ！
Let Zero go!
てめえらは ゼロの親友　この玉城真一郎様が相手 ぐわあ～～！
You're about to face his best pal,
Shinichiro Tamaki, so...
くっそぉ!何で俺はいっつも～～！
Dammit! Why does this
always happen to me?!
Right! Now's my chance!
よし　今なら
待っていたよ ゼロ
Just what I was waiting for, Zero!
攻撃する瞬間にはシールドは張れまい
You can't raise your shield in
the moment when you attack!
Now, to blow what you
value most to atoms!
さあおまえの大事なものを飛び散らせろ！
こ このポジションでは
In... In this position, I can't!
ナナリー！
Nunnally!
ん？
え やられたの
What? They got me?
Kewell!
キューエル！
先日はどうもブリタニアの吸血鬼さん
Hello from the other day,
Mr. Vampire of Britannia.
Ah...
ほう
K-Kallen?!
カ カレンか？
ゼロ！
Zero! Kallen Kouzuki,
captain of your personal guard...
親衛隊隊長　紅月カレン
has now returned to the front line!
ただいまをもって戦線に復帰しました
ドロボー！僕の～！僕の！
Thieves! That's mine! It's mine!
Not quite, sir.
I improved it too, remember?
違いますよ
私も改良していますから
はいおっしゃるとおりです
Uh, right. Like you said.
ってあ　いやそんなことじゃなくって
Wha... No, that's not what I mean!
もしこれをつかいこなせるデヴァイサーが乗っているとしたら
If the pilot is a Devicer who
could handle that machine,
even at 60% output, it would be!
60％の出力でも
プリン伯爵とあれはセシルのエナジーウィングか
That's the Earl of Pudding's work!
And Cécile's energy wings, too!
あいつら勝手にあたしの紅蓮を
How dare they do that to my
Guren without permission!
Still, now that we've got Kallen back...
しかし これでカレンがもどってこられたわけだし
We're at our full fighting strength!
戦力は整った
ブラッドリー卿 紅蓮の破壊許可がおりました
Sir Bradley, you have permission
to destroy the Guren.
Irrelevant! Killing is all one
should do on the battlefield!
関係ない戦場にいる以上殺すだけだ
Whoops!
おっと
イレヴンよ戦場の真実を知っているか？
Eleven!
Do you know the truth of the battlefield?
Kill a man normally,
and it's considered a crime.
日常で人を殺せば罪になるが戦場ならば　殺した数だけ英雄となる
But kill many on the battlefield
and you become a hero!
ふ～んブリタニアの吸血鬼さんは英雄になりたいわけ？
So, Mr. Vampire of Britannia
wants to be a hero, is that it?
いいや公に人の大事なものを
No. I'm saying I like to officially take lives,
that which people value the most!
命を奪えるとは最高じゃないかって話さ
You know...
あんたさあ ちょっと下品だよ
you're not much of a gentleman!
これで！
And now...
What was that?
それが何か？
通じないよ
That won't work with me!
But now I've drawn you in close!
いいやこれで間合いはつまった
何？
Wh-What?!
質問あなたの大事なものは何？
Question: What do you value the most?
自分の命だけなの？
Is it just your own life?
You think an Eleven can threaten me?!
脅しのつもりか？イレヴンが！
Goodbye.
さようなら
奪われる？この私の命が
My life! My life has been taken?!
このサルがぁ～～～！
By a monkey like you?!
よくやった！カレン
Good work, Kallen! Now get back to the
government bureau and get Nunnally!
あとは政庁に戻り ナナリーを！
I won't let you!
そうはさせない！
くっ
枢木スザク！
Suzaku Kururugi!
Whoops!
おっと
くっ
カレン！どくんだ！
Kallen! Stand aside!
I will not, Suzaku!
どけないよ！スザク
防いだ？ハドロンブラスターを？
It deflected it?! The hadron blaster?
カレンやっぱりシュタットフェルトの名前より
Kallen! So, you chose the name
Kouzuki over Stadtfeld in the end.
紅月をえらんだわけか
そうね
That's right.
だから　ジノ
So, Gino... Should I be happy or sad
that we meet again on the battlefield?
戦場であえたことを喜ぶべきかしら
悲しむべきかしら
ふふ楽しむべきってのはどうだい？
How about we just enjoy it?
スザクカレンとの決着は残しておいてくれよ
Suzaku! Leave Kallen for me
to settle things with!
だってさ スザク
The problem with that, Suzaku...
すまない ジノ
I'm sorry, Gino.
そんな余裕が許される相手ではなさそうだ
She's not the sort of opponent
you should play around with.
Tohdoh's forces have broken through
to the enemy's headquarters!
藤堂軍が敵本陣に突撃をかけました
そんな！このガレスが！
Impossible! My Gareth!
フォースエリアにシールドをはりなさい
Raise shields in area four!
狙うはシュナイゼルの首級のみ
We're just after Schneizel's head!
Assume Slash and Encircle Formation!
斬撃包囲陣をしかける！
藤堂さん 木下副隊長の証言データをおくります
Tohdoh! I'm sending you data
sub-commander Kinoshita kept as testimony!
This is hardly the time!
なんだ？こんなときに
きいてもらえればわかります
Just listen to it and you'll understand!
We can't trust Zero!
やはりゼロは信用できません
ん？
I'm heading into the government
bureau to capture Rolo!
僕はこれから政庁にはいり ロロを捕縛します
艦内　第４イ號区画にて爆発反応あり！
Explosion detected in section 4-I of the ship!
No... Could it be Chigusa?
まさか 千草か？
How do I turn this into a close-range battle?
近接戦闘にもちこもうにも！
スザク！あなたの相手はカレンじゃない！
Suzaku! Kallen isn't the one you
should be fighting! It's Zero!
ゼロでしょう！
脱出ルートはイケブクロ方面です
Your escape route is
towards the Ikebukuro front.
Just to be safe, launch after we've mopped up
the Black Knights remaining in your flight path.
万が一に備えルート上の黒の騎士団を掃討したあと発進します
ゼロ様！総督を発見しました
Master Zero, we've found the viceroy!
そうかよくやった！
I see! Good work!
ロロ様はナイトメアを鹵獲した後
Master Rolo said he'll escort us out of
here after he secures a Knightmare.
こちらの護衛につくとのことですが
わかったこれで勝利条件はそろった
Understood! Now, all the
conditions for victory are in place.
カレン！いっきにスザクを討て！
Kallen! Finish off Suzaku now!
そうすれば邪魔者はいなくなる！
Do that and nothing will stand in our way!
はい！
Yes, sir!
逃げるんだ枢木卿！
Get out of there, Sir Kururugi!
今のランスロットじゃ
The Lancelot's no match as it is!
でも ゼロが！
But, Zero is!
Oh, you!
この
朴念仁！
You stubborn fool!
ち ちがいすぎる
It's... It's too great...
The difference in machine potential!
マシンポテンシャルが
殿下このままでは ブラッドリー卿に続き枢木卿まで
Highness, at this rate, we're going to
lose Sir Kururugi along with Sir Bradley!
撃ってよ！スザク！フレイヤなら！とニーナ
Shoot it, Suzaku!
The F.L.E.I.J.A. can beat them!
だめだ
No! In the end, this is just a threat!
If we actually use it, then!
これはあくまで脅し
使ってしまったら
勝てない
I can't win...
さようなら　スザク
Goodbye, Suzaku.
ナナリー様！
Miss Nunnally!
殺せ！スザクを！
Kill Suzaku now!
Fire the F.L.E.I.J.A.!
You'll save yourself!
撃ってよ！フレイヤを！
あなたも助かるのに！
But, if I do that!
でも それだけは
Even if it costs me my life here!
たとえ ここで死ぬとしても
そうだこれが償いなんだ
That's right... This is redemption.
受け入れるしかないここで
All I can do is take it.
Now I'm going to!
俺は
I...
生きろ！
LIVE!
おぉ 俺は　生きる
I... have to live!
これは フレイヤか？
Is this... F.L.E.I.J.A.?
ひけ！全軍後退！
Fall back! All units, retreat!
なぜブリタニア軍が後退を？
Why are the Britannian forces retreating?
我が軍もさがるぞ
We have to retreat, too!
Asahina, do you read me?!
朝比奈きこえてるか？
政庁からでろ！朝比奈！
Get out of the government bureau!
Asahina!
何かまずい
Something's wrong!
Pull the Ikaruga back, maximum speed!
斑鳩を最大戦速で後退させろ
You in the Sutherland, what are you doing?!
They've fired the F.L.E.I.J.A.!
そこのサザーランド！何をやっている！
フレイヤだぞ！
フレイヤ？
F.L.E.I.J.A.?
まさか あれがスザクの言っていた
Could that be the weapon
Suzaku mentioned before?
ああ ナナリー！！！！
NUNNALLY!!!
Tohdoh... I tried to warn you!
藤堂さん 僕はあなたに
Why did they use the F.L.E.I.J.A. here?!
なぜここでフレイヤを！
姫様 お逃げください！姫様!!!
Princess, save yourself!
PRINCESS!!!
姫様  生きてください
Princess, please live! You must live!
生きて
ロロ
Rolo...
はい 兄さん
Yes, big brother?
ナナリーと話をさせてくれないか？
Could you let me speak
with Nunnally, please?
Um... Well...
あっ その
咲世子につながらなくってさ
I can't seem to reach Sayoko.
あの 兄さん
Look... Big brother...
We weren't in time.
まにあわなかったんだ
ナナリーはあの光の中に
Nunnally was caught in that light.
そんなことをきいているんじゃないんだ
I'm not asking you that.
ナナリーと話したいんだ
I just want to talk to Nunnally.
でも ナナリーは死んだんだ
But... Nunnally is dead!
She's dead, big brother!
死んだんだよ兄さん
うそをつくな！
DON'T LIE TO ME!
なあロロほんの少しでいいんだ
Please, Rolo.
Just for a moment...
ナナリーと 話をさせてくれ
Please...
Just let me speak to Nunnally.
Dakuse wa oni
This corrupt world is filled with demons
Seigi wa nanzo to
What is justice?
Tou mae ni aragae yo
Resist, don't just question
Akutoku no hana
The flower of evil
Gizen no yume
Dreams of hypocrisy
Mishi me niwa me wo sashi
Give your gaze to the eyes that see them
Sei mo ja mo wakatareru koto nashi
The line between right and wrong cannot be known
Hikari wa tae taiji no you ni
Light is gone, and you slumber
Kimi wa nemuru yami no shikyuu
Like an unborn child in the womb of darkness
Kodoku koso itooshii
Isolation is what you love
ルルーシュだ　今週も楽しんでくれてありがとう
Yui-itsu no mikata to naru darou
It will probably be your only ally
いつも応援してくれるみんなにご覧のプレゼントを送る
Hitori hitori chishio ni mamire
One by one, stained with the tide of blood
パスーワードを入力して　こちらのケータイサイトから応募してほしい
Kono jidai ni umare ochita
You were born into this era
今から一時間限定の受付だ
Erabareshi oujira yo
Oh, chosen princes
もちろん　特製の待受けもあるぞ
それでは諸君　来週のお楽しみに
Tatakai koso shukuen
Battle shall be your banquet
Aa ware wa uruwashii zenchi
Oh, I am graceful omniscience
Ai no haha
The loving mother
Kimi wo umu
Who bore you
Kono chichi ni hagukumishi mono wa
The ones who were raised on my breast
Jigoku no harakara
Are your brethren in hell
Mokushi no in
The mark of apocalypse
Shinri wa nanzo to
What is truth
Shirimosezu uzumoreshi intoku no tane
A seed of secrecy buried where no one knows
Moroha no ken
A double-edged sword
Nuku ha niwa ha wo muke
Turn its blade upon the unsheathed blade
Mamorubeki mono dake wo shinjite
Believe only in what you must protect
Aru ga mama ni kimi wa
And in your own way
Kimi wo hanate
You'll set yourself free
BETRAYAL